It turns out that this left string, this stuff to the left
原来左边的这根线，左边的这个东西
of the vertical bar can be implemented by a stack, and that's because we only do
可以由堆栈实现，这是因为我们只做
reduced operations immediately to the left of the vertical bar. So it's always suffix
减少了紧邻竖线左侧的操作。所以它总是后缀
of the string to left of the vertical bar, where the reduction is happening so what a
垂直线条左边的字符串的位置，这里发生了减少，那么这是什么呢？
shift move then does is to push a terminal onto the stack. It reads one token of
Shift Move接下来要做的是将终端推送到堆栈上。它读取一个令牌
input, and pushed it onto the stack. And then a reduce, pops some number symbols
输入，并将其推送到堆栈上。然后是减号，弹出一些数字符号
off of the stack. That's the production right hand side. And then it pushed one
离开堆栈。那是产品的右手边。然后它推了一个
non-terminal onto the stack. And that's the production, left hand side. Now it can
将非终端拖到堆栈上。这就是制作，在左手边。现在它可以了
happen that in a given state, that more than one action, shift or reduce, may lead
在给定状态下，可能会导致不止一个动作，即Shift或Reduce
to a valid parse. So in particular, if it's legal to shift or reduce, if you can
转换为有效的解析。所以特别要注意的是，如果移动或减少是合法的，如果你可以
do either one of those things, then we say there is a shift re duce conflict. The
做这两件事中的任何一件，那么我们就说这是一种转变，减少了冲突。这个
parser could either read one token of input and push it on the stack, or it
解析器可以读取一个输入标记并将其推送到堆栈上，或者它
could perform a reduction. If it's legal to reduce by two different productions,
可以进行减量。如果减少两种不同的产品是合法的，
then there is what is called a reduce/reduce conflict. Okay. So reduce,
然后是所谓的减少/减少冲突。好吧。所以减少，
reduce conflicts are, are always bad, are almost always bad. They indicate usually
减少冲突是，总是不好的，几乎总是不好的。他们通常表示
some kind of serious problem with the grammar. Shift reduce conflicts are not
语法有一些严重的问题。Shift Reduce冲突不是
good, but they're often easier to remove. So if you have reduce, reduce conflicts
很好，但是它们通常更容易去掉。所以如果你减少了，那就减少冲突
particularly when you're building your, grammar for cool, then you're doing
特别是当你在构建你的，酷的语法时，你就是在做
something seriously wrong. If you have shift reduce conflicts then that, that's
出了严重的问题。如果你有减少冲突的班次，那么，那就是
to be almost expected, because of You're probably going to need to use precedence
几乎是意料之中的，因为您可能需要使用优先顺序
declarations, Remove them, and we'll talk about that some more in another video. But
声明，删除它们，我们将在另一个视频中详细讨论这一点。但
in general, if you have either one of these conflicts, it means that, there's
一般来说，如果你有这些冲突中的任何一个，那就意味着，有
some state in which the parser doesn't know what to do. And you either need to
解析器不知道该做什么的某种状态。你要么需要
rewrite the grammar, or give it a hint as to what it should do in order to
重写语法，或者给它一个提示，说明它应该做什么，以便
successfully parse your language.
成功解析您的语言。